Research and Dean of Graduate Studies, Office of the Vice President for; Records ua400
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 1997 May 15 addition, 1982-1995; 9 cubic ft.
  - Computer Science, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Economics, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - English, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - French Studies, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Germanic + Slavic Languages + Literatures, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Geography + Planning, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - History, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Latin American & Caribbean Studies, 1981; 1985-1994 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - LACS - Title VI, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Linguistics + Cognitive Science, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Mathematics and Statistics, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Music, 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Philosophy, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Physics, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Psychology, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Russian and East European Studies Program, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Sociology, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Center for Applied Psychological Research, 1986-1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Center for Social and Demographic Analysis, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Center for Stress and Anxiety, 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - X-Ray Optical Systems, Inc., 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Professional Development Program, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Center for Tech in Government, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dean, Sch. Of Criminal Justice, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - School of Info Science and Policy, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Center for Legislative Development, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - School of Social Welfare - Deans Office, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Info Science P.H.D Program, 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Dean's - School of Business, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Hindelang Criminal Justice Res. CTR., 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Center For Women in Government, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - University Center for Policy Research Memoranda and Performance Evaluations, 1987-1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - School of Education Dean's OFC, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Healthcare Management Presentation [ 1 of 2 ], 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Healthcare Management Presentation [ 2 of 2 ], 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Excelsior School of Science and Mathematics for the State of NY, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Beginning Inc., 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Educational Administration, 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Educational Psych and Statistics, 1989; 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Reading, 1989-1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Educational Theory and Practice, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - CASDA, 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Center on Literature Teaching and Learning, 1991 January 1-1996 January 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - University Research Center for Writing and Literacy, 1982-1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Child Research and Studies Center, 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 2-YR College Dev. CTR, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - School of Public Health - Deans OFC Sciences, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - School of Public Health/ Health Research Inc. SPHS/HRI, 1983-1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Excellence in Research Awards, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Awards for Excellence in Academic Service, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - FRAP Category B, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - FRAP Category A, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - FRAP A, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Research Awards Program (FRAP) Category A, 1995 April-1996 April (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - FRAP B, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Conference and Journals, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Journals and Conferences, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Journals and Conferences, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Journals and Conferences, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Conferences and Journals, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Journals and Conferences, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Administrative Records, 1999 April 20 addition, 1993-1997; 4 cubic ft.
  This series contains university employee disclosure statements and related memoranda. This series also contains a number of files documenting the process of handing out research grants and awards, including FRAP and the Albany Benevolent Association Grant Awards. The series also contains several folders of correspondence sent both to and from the Office of Research and Graduate Studies. Finally, this series includes correspondence with a number of international universities regarding both proposed and implemented cooperative degree programs.
  - Disclosure Statements SUNY 2s, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - SUNY Form 2's, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Disclosure Statements (General Correspondence), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Disclosure Statements A-G, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Disclosure Statements H-R, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Disclosure Statements S-Z, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Disclosure Statements (General Correspondence), 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Disclosure Statements A-K, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Disclosure Statements L-Z, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Disclosure Statements (General Correspondence), 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Disclosure Statements A-L, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Disclosure Statements M-Z, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Disclosure Statements (General Correspondence), 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Disclosure Statements A-J, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Disclosure Statements K-Z, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Distinguished Service Professor, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Journals and Conferences, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Distinguished Service Professor, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Distinguished Service Professor Nominations, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - FRAP Category A, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Journal & Conference Support, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Conference & Journal Support, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Excellence in Research, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Tilney, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Excellence in Research Awards, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - FRAP Category B, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Excellence in Academic Service Awards, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Research Equipment & Renovation Program, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - GRI, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - GRI Allocation, 1993-1994; 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - GRI, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Office of Research and Graduate Studies, Camp Liberty Grant Memo, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - GRI Financial Transactions, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - GRE Grant Acct. #50002, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - GRI Financial Transactions, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - GRI Financial Transactions, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Council on Research Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Council on Research Meetings, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Research Incentives Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Research/ Research Foundation Interface Committee, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Research Incentive Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Enervated Grant Request (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Enervated Grant Request (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Benevolent Grants Fall, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Benevolent Assoc., 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Benevolent Association Grant, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - BENEVOLENT GRANT, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - BENEVOLENT, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Benevolent Awards, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Department Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Departmental Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Research Foundation, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Departmental Correspondence, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Departmental Correspondence, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Departmental Correspondence, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Departmental Correspondence, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bambina Chinese Studies, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Brazilian Agriculture Research Corp., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - China, 1990; 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Council on Research, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - COSTA RICA, 1987-1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CIES: Council for International Exchange of Scholars, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cyprus, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - del Salvador, Universidad Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Graduate: Application Fees TAP, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Assistants/ Teaching Assistants, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Tuition Scholarship (GSLU), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Hungary Democratic Institution Building (Baaklini), 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hungary Summer Academic Program (A. Shane), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hungarian Univ. Management Training Project, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Indonesia, 1985-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hebrew University of Israel Program Evolution, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - International University (Moscow, RV), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Japan, 1989-1995; 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Korea, 1991-1993; 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Legon University, Ghana, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Morehouse College, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Moscow State University, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Office of Research and Graduate Studies Nankai University PHD Program Correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Pakistan, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Puerto Rico, 1991; 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Tribhuvan University Kathmandu, Nepal, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - University of Salerno Italy, 1987-1991 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Spain, 1989-1990; 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Sophia University (Bulgaria), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Somalia SOMTAD, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - TAP (Tuition Assistance Program), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Yaound University Yaound, Cameroon, 1986-1993 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Administrative Records, 2001 addition, 1980-2001; 9.4 cubic ft.
  Files in this series have been maintained in their original order upon transfer. A number of partially full boxes within this series were consolidated with original file order maintained.
  Materials in this collection include documents regarding research policies, including documentation on conflicts of interest as well as both human and animal testing. This series also contains correspondence and documentation on University-affiliated research centers and institutes. This series also includes the Research Foundation's documentation on Y2K compliance as well as the University's implementation of Oracle software through the OASIS program.
  - A-21 Indirect Costs, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Institute of Government, 1986-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Conflict of Interest SUNY and RF and NIH, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University at Albany Research Foundation Policy on Financial Conflicts of Interest, 2000 December 12
    - Conflict of Interest SUNY and RF and NIH, 1989-1995
  - Research Foundation, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Continuous Quality Improvement Program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Computer Services Advisory Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Human Subjects, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Memo to Deans, Department Chairs and Directors from Jeanna Gullahorn Re: Compliance with Human and Animal Subjects Regulations, 1992 August 19
    - Memo and attachment from Anne Connelly to Carl Carlucci re: Human Subjects Audit, 1998 May 6
  - Misconduct in Research, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Research Office, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - DSS/MOU, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - DSS Audit and Investigation, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Technology, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CAT Industrial Advisory Board, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CAT - SIA Center in Interconnects, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CAT - Advisory Committee for Academic and Technical Programs, 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CAT - Economic Outreach Board, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Advanced Thin Film Technology, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Center for Advanced Thin Film Technology, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Center for Advanced Technology, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Center for Environmental Sciences and Technology Management [ 1 of 2 ], 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Center for Environmental Sciences and Technology Management [ 2 of 2 ], 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - CESTM, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - CESTM Schematic Reports, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sharon Dawes, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CTG, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ASRC, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Office of the Provost, 1994-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Legal Affairs, 1985-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Vice Chancellor for Educational Technology, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Vice Chancellor for Capital Facilities, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - International Programs - SUNY Ctrl, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Finance and Bus, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Academic Programs, Policy and Planning, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - SUNY Rethinking, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Vice Chancellor for Univ. Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - RAM (Resource Allocation Methodology, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - SUNY Research Council, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Advisory Group for the Review of Central Office Operations and Processes, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - CAT Funding Proposal, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Master Plan Report, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Strategic Plan for 1999-2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Educational Fliers, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Organizational Chart, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Research Foundation Strategic Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Research Binder, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Centers and Institutes Policies, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 12K Compliance Tracking Report, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Albany Institute for Research in Education Binder, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - University Police Department Building Proposal, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Research Center Update Memorandums, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - SUNY Policy Handbook, 1983 Update, 1983 September 13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Joint Laboratory for Advanced Materials Progress Report, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - CASDA Research Achievement Expeditions and Progress Report, 1992 February (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Center for Molecular Genetics Report, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Center Reports [ 1 of 2 ], 1991-1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Center Reports [ 2 of 2 ], 1991-1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Center for Policy Research Progress Report, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Capital Area School Development Association Planning Document, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ASRC Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ctr. For Policy Research, 1988 January-1992 February (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Universities and Bulletins, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Office Expenditures [ 1 of 4 ], 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Office Expenditures [ 2 of 4 ], 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Office Expenditures [ 3 of 4 ], 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Office Expenditures [ 4 of 4 ], 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Research Brochures from Other Universities, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - SUNY Albany Research Brochures, 1981-2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - University at Albany Foundation Fund Manages Manual, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1990-2000 Self Study Report (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1990-2000 Self Study Appendices (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Institute for Environmental Health Proposal, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Thunderstorm Analysis Center (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Center for Electronic Language Learning and Research (CELLAR) Proposal, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Middle States Commission Visit Review, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - New York States Ethics Commission SUNY Academic Filers Financial Disclosure Manual, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Diversity Budget Request [ 1 of 2 ], 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Diversity Budget Request [ 2 of 2 ], 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Arts and Sciences College, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Albert Charels Mossin Endowment for the Physical and Life Sciences, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Africana Studies, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Anthropology, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Art, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Department of biological Sciences Correspondence and Proposal [ 1 of 2 ], 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Department of biological Sciences Correspondence and Proposal [ 2 of 2 ], 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Chemistry, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Classics, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Communication, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Computer Science, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Computing Center, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Dept. of Earth & Atmospheric Sciences Approved, 1996 July 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NOAA Cooperative Institute [ 1 of 2 ], 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NOAA Cooperative Institute [ 2 of 2 ], 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - East Asian Studies, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Economics, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - English, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Project Renaissance, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - French Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Geography & Planning, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hispanic & Italian Studies, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Spanish, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - History, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Judaic Studies, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Languages, Literature, & Cultures, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Latin American & Caribbean Studies, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Mathematics & Statistics, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Performing Arts Center, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Department of Philosophy, 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Physics, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - G. Oehrlein, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - NSF Instrumentation Reviews for Susanne M. Lee, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Physics - Personnel, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Psychology, 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Sociology, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Theatre, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Women's Studies, 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Awards, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - CESTM II Space Comm., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Environment, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Future Faculty/ Administrator Fellows (Tuition Scholarships), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Assistantships/ Fellowships, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - GRI, 1992; 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Student Organization, 1991-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - International (agreement sample, misc.), 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Proposals, Letters, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Master Planning, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Minority Students, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1987-1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Research (misc: articles, reports, etc.), 1992 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Space - General, 1986-1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 423 State Street, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - State Street #423, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Michael DiResta, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Tuition ( General,Graduate,Scholarships,Reimbursemnt,Fees), 1995; 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Stony Brook Engineering, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Stony Brook, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Student Complaints, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - University Center/ Old Westbury, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Albany, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - University Centers: Binghamton, 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - University Center Univ. at Buffalo, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Albany Medical Center - Collaboration, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Superfund and Bush Lab Correspondence [ 1 of 2], 1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Superfund and Bush Lab Correspondence [ 2 of 2], 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - School of Public Health Self Study and Site Visit [ 1 of 3 ], 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - School of Public Health Self Study and Site Visit [ 2 of 3 ], 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - School of Public Health Self Study and Site Visit [ 3 of 3 ], 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Distance Learning Program, 1980-1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Center for Biometry and Statistics Correspondence and Memoranda [ 1 of 2 ], 1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Center for Biometry and Statistics Correspondence and Memoranda [ 2 of 2 ], 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Public Health School Foundation, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - NYS Department of Health Correspondence, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - School of Public Health/ NYS Department of Health Correspondence, 1991-1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Cabinet (mtg. materials from Cabinet folder), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - NRC Study - Doctoral Program, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - National Research Council, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Research! America, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Great Lakes Research Consortium, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller Institute of Government, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller College, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Professional Development Program, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - School of Criminal Justice Presidents Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Dean - Graduate School of Public Affairs, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Political Science, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Public Administration, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - School of Public Health Presidents Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Dean - School of Business, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Business MBA, 1988-1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - David Brinberg (Confidential), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - School of Education, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Counseling Psychology, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Educational Administration, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - CASDA, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Educational Theory and Practice, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - New York State Common Retirement Fund, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Library, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Sponsored Funds, 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - International Student Office, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Internal Audits, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Institutional Services, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Human Resources, 1992-1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Office of Institutional Research Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Resource Allocation Files, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Accounting, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Equipment Management Office, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Environmental Health and Safety, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Budget Request, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Financial Management & Budget Office, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Office of International Programs, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Information Systems & Technology, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - VP for University Advancement, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Gifts/Donations to Univ., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - University at Albany Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Integrated Administrative System Project (IAS Project), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Associate Vice President & Controller, 1988-1997 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs Search Memos and Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Vice President for Finance and Business Memoranda and Correspondence, 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - VP for Research, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Wharton-IRHE Exec. Education Prgm. General - Vice President, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Christopher D'Elia Correspondence [ 1 of 3 ], 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)